Chime
優しい陽だまりにチャイムがディレイする
頬を撫でる風、息吹は深く鳴ってゆく
遠回りの涙、名前付けた明日
重なる未来のノーライン
See you next time.
Well, it's just that it's cold today.
It reminds me it's almost New Year's, so...
Almost?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, it's close.
Um, it's still November, though.
Hey!
There he is.
Ah, morning.
It's real chilly today, ain't it?
He's in his blazer.
Why do you sound so excited about that?
So refreshing.
I haven't seen it since spring.
Huh?
Uh...
You noticed, huh?
This mess.
Oh, your hair!
So that wasn't it?
Oh, man.
Then I should have told you my bedhead was just a new hairstyle.
Oh, my hair!
Kaze Haya!
Hey!
Come here, I got something awesome to show you!
Awesome?
Okay, see you around.
He said it was his bedhead.
How cute!
That?
It's the new Ogura flavor!
The juice box version of Hayakuni Nishu!
When Kaze Haya is surrounded by everyone like this...
I love how happy he seems.
Oh, yeah.
I used to think...
It's incredible how they gather around him.
I want to be more like that one day.
You're turning red!
Just as the seasons change, over time, little by little, my feelings start to as well.
Oh, my gosh.
This is getting so annoying.
Your boyfriend?
Yep.
That same college student?
Yeah.
Every single day and every single night, he's like,
What are you doing?
Who are you with?
Let's meet up right now.
Why don't you reply right away?
But why can't you come out?
Are you with a guy?
Like...
I wake up in the morning, then I go to school, after that I'm in class with my friends all day!
And at night, I'm just sleeping!
Yeah, that is true.
But seriously, Yano-jin, why are you dating a guy like that?
He...
asked.
I wonder why guys are like this.
They act mature and grown up, but then they show their true colors.
I used to think it was such a pain in the butt to hang out with girls, that they were catty.
But guys are so much worse.
Oh, is that how it is?
No.
This is just a really problematic example.
You'd have to love someone a lot to be that invested.
Seems romantic relationships come in all sorts of farms.
Oh, Ryo.
Hmm?
I'm coming over tonight, so be home.
Sure.
Let me keep playing that one game from where I left off.
Okay, but...
Or, how about a fighting game?
Definitely not.
When Chizu and Sanada are together, their energies really match each other.
My eyes are only for Chizuru.
Yes, I can't think of two people who would be better together.
A perfect pair.
But I wonder how she feels.
If I had to guess, I think she probably...
likes him back.
Oh, Pops.
Hi there.
Yo, sup, Chizu?
It's cold.
Oh, I'll help during winter break again.
Okay?
Uh, we appreciate it.
Good to have our poster girl around.
Yeah, I guess it is, isn't it?
I'm gonna head upstairs now.
Sure.
But I mean it when I say it, Chizu.
I really do wish you were our daughter.
If it were my choice, you know I would be.
Already going to bed?
You took too long.
What the hell?
I told you I was coming.
Wait!
Ah, dammit, I died!
Stupid lion!
Chimera, you mean?
That reminds me of you talking in your sleep.
Huh?
I have never once talked in my sleep.
Little thing.
How dare.
The dumb lion chimera.
So, by the way...
Is, um, there anything on your wish list, Rio?
Hmm.
Under 500 yen.
A new baseball glove?
500 yen!
Not shoulder massage tickets.
I'd be okay with anything.
So, thank you.
I never actually said I'm getting you something!
Sure.
Thanks anyway.
I'm leaving.
Okay.
Oh, I meant to ask.
On New Year's...
Uh, actually, never mind.
It's nothing.
Good night!
I see.
That's what you wanted to talk about.
Hello?
Yeah.
Dad's taking a bath right now.
Sure.
Wait, next week?
I gotta tell her soon, huh?
Sawako, Yono-chin!
Hey, shop with me today!
Shopping!
Oh, no, I can't.
Huh?
Why?
Because I'm meeting my boyfriend.
And I need to see him as soon as possible.
Bye.
Uh, um...
Hmm?
I'm so afraid.
Seriously?
Awesome!
W-what are you buying?
Hmm?
Oh, uh...
I'm getting Ryu a present for his birthday.
It's coming up soon.
Oh!
Yes, that's great!
Well, you know, I'm like a crazy loyal friend, so...
Let me go!
Ow!
Get out of here to chill, Joe!
You don't understand!
She's always looking at me with this passionate gaze!
You're the one who's looking at her like that!
You probably don't even know her name, do you?
Hey, do you happen to believe in destiny?
Listen, can't you hear it drawing near?
The deafening sound of our combined fate's footsteps!
Yes, I've indeed come to return your feelings!
Ew.
Get up!
Pull it together!
You gotta stand up, Joe!
No!
What did you give him last year?
Shoulder massage tickets, cause I was broke.
Shoulder massage tickets?
He chose to use them all up right there on the spot.
Massaged his shoulders for three full hours.
Wow!
She must really care about Sonata's physical health, huh?
This year, I've got a 500 yen budget.
It's perfect!
A new baseball glove is out of the question, but maybe a glove bag?
Hold this for a sec.
Yes!
What now?
I do have enough!
Sweet!
Then I guess I'll be extra generous this year!
Love!
That was the perfect purchase!
I'm really happy for you, Chizu!
A mini skirt?
Well, I thought it might be a good idea to change up my style once in a while.
I want to ask.
I wonder if it's okay to, or is it bad.
But...
If I go with my gut, right now seems like a good time.
Um, Jisoo, I was wondering if you have a crush on someone.
I did it!
What the heck? That's so random. I do.
It's always been a one-sided thing, though.
Always?
Yeah, I've had this little crush for a super long time.
Wait, then. Does that mean...
We've been friends since childhood.
I knew it!
The problem is, he really just thinks of me as a little sister.
That's not true!
Huh? Say what?
It's a... punch?
It's fine, really. I'm okay with it.
I'm a kid, after all. There's no way I'm even on his radar.
I totally understand.
That's why I've decided I'm gonna become a real catch.
Once I grow up, you never know, right?
I'm glad I ended up asking her.
I've never seen Jisoo with an expression like this before.
But still, I don't get to see him much these days. I miss him.
Huh?
He lives way up in Sapporo, so there's not much I can do about that.
Oh.
He didn't come back for last, Obon, either.
Which means it's been almost a year now.
But I know for sure he'll be coming back for New Year's.
And he better watch out, because I'm a full-blown high school girl now.
Wait.
What?
I'm getting kind of confused, so...
Is it okay if I ask this straight out?
What's up?
So the person you've been talking about...
You mean Sanada, right, Jisoo?
Huh?
Sawako, wait.
Did you think I was talking about Ryu?
Uh...
Mm-hmm.
You've got it all wrong.
We've grown up together, so he's more like a brother than anything else.
Though I wouldn't mind if we actually became siblings.
You think of him as a brother?
See, the person I like is...
His older brother.
Huh?
Oh, man.
Makes me blush.
Um...
Huh?
Does Sanada...
Know all of that?
Real?
There's no way he wouldn't know.
So this whole time, he already knew.
Why?
Uh...
No reason.
Really, it's nothing.
Huh?
Second!
Can't hear you, Sanada!
Right!
You guys, too!
Again!
You hadn't gone home yet?
Well, the gang and I were trying to cheer Joe up.
As reckless as usual, I see.
But yeah, we decided we're gonna throw him a party to help him get back on his feet.
Care to join us?
We're thinking next weekend.
Next weekend?
Oh, that doesn't really work for me.
Oh?
You got plans?
Not exactly, but...
Hmm?
That's when...
My brother's back home.
What about something like this?
Looks cold.
You'd really have to brace yourself.
I'd be shivering.
That's no problem, because I'm all fired up!
Plus...
Jesus is glowing right now.
Would've made it in love.
I get it.
Seeing the person you like can make you so incredibly happy.
Oh, hey, Ryu.
Morning.
Night.
Good morning.
Morning.
Hmm?
Hey, what's up?
Hi, good morning.
Kasehaya, what do you think about these?
What's that?
Winter stuff?
Yep, a mini skirt.
Huh.
How much do those go for?
Looks like 15,000 ye...
I forgot I was dead broke right now.
I really wanted to have it for New Year's.
Oh, New Year's?
You don't get some cash then, right?
No, that's too late.
I don't know how long Toru's staying.
It may just be New Year's Eve or di-
I, uh...
So his name is Toru, huh?
I didn't say anything just now.
I didn't, right?
Uh, yeah, I guess not.
What's with all the drama, you guys?
Oh, Yanochi!
We broke up.
So we dumped you?
No, I dumped him!
And it was a total nightmare.
Yeah, can definitely see that.
I was honest about how I felt and gently suggested breaking up, and he...
Oh, I'm sorry.
I-I didn't mean to.
You're the only thing I have left, Yanochi.
Let's move in together, okay?
Please?
This is pointless.
The guy isn't listening to a single word coming out of my mouth.
But yeah, I didn't really like him.
He was just totally annoying.
Wow, sorry.
I assumed you were into him.
After all my complaining, that was your takeaway?
I want to comfort her, but I can't think of the right words to say.
I know that it wasn't meant to be.
But at the same time, it's not any fun when things have to end like this, either.
Poor thing!
Huh?
What's going on with you?
Why are you acting like I was the one who got dumped?
There's someone else who got dumped here?
Comrades and heartbreak!
Don't lump me in with you!
Any kind of romance involves some sort of heartbreak.
But it's still tough each time.
Like I said, I'm the one who did the breaking up, not him!
Hide your pain from me!
Come on, let's talk about it together!
Let's be honest, or are you, Yano?
Ryu.
Hmm?
You haven't told Yoshida yet, have you?
Well, it isn't easy to bring it up.
Do you think you'd tell her, or...
Would I?
Hmm.
I think I would.
And the rest, that's on her.
That's not my call.
Hmm.
I figured you might say that, Shota.
Huh?
Well, you're probably right, though.
Because if Chizuru doesn't know, and we end up running into my brother, it's gonna be a real problem.
Hmm.
But still, it's hard.
New Year's?
A mini skirt?
Sounds great to me.
Really?
Good.
I'm thinking about getting a frilly one.
Uh, get one that looks good on you.
Uh, you think it'd look bad?
This is real girl talk.
I'm so curious.
I wonder what kind of guy he is.
Hey, can we go see him, too?
What?
No.
I think I'd die.
Jesus seems so happy.
Oh, no.
I'm getting all excited about myself.
Even though our Yano is suffering.
I'm fine.
You really don't have to worry about it.
I'm so sorry, Yano.
You have to cheer up.
Hey, why don't we throw an awesome party to help get your spirits up?
We can use my house.
Uh, yeah, sure.
Then let's have a sleepover on Friday.
You too, Sawago.
Sleepover?
I can come, too?
We're all going to play a fighting game together.
Oh, a game?
Chizuru, it's me.
Huh?
I'm coming in.
Hey!
Shh!
Don't just barge in here without permission.
I could have been changing clothes or something.
Yeah, yeah.
And I could say the exact same thing to you.
What's up?
It's a rare treat for you to come visit me.
Here.
Hmm.
You don't want any?
Huh?
We should talk.
Hmm?
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
Chizuru, here's the thing.
No, go home!
Hmm?
Just leave.
Get out of here!
No, but I need to talk.
Ow!
What am I supposed to do?
Up until now, just interacting with others
was enough to overwhelm me.
Because that alone was so difficult.
I never even thought about romance.
But I'm sure that romantic relationships
must be just as difficult as friendship.
The reason I can understand that, at least a little,
is probably because of how certain I am
that I've fallen in love with Kaze Haya.
No way!
わからないそれが答えなんだって
シャボンタモ飛ばそう
空まではきっと届かないうちに壊れそう
噛んだで知りたいの永遠じゃない
このま
But I'll make it important to see only one plane.
From here, I'll be able to find you as a lecture.
Next time, dream.